So my story very short okay I spent 25
years in a monastery
then at the end you have examination
and uh it takes 3 weeks and uh in my
monastery there are about at that time
about 1,300
monks and then they say okay now you
have to do examination and each monk
will come asking question finish they
give you this big yellow hat
everybody Everybody wants one in the
monastery. Everybody wants to get a hat.
Why? If you get that hat, then rest of
your life you can relax,
drink tea,
teach the little ones, you know, and not
so difficult. So I got the yellow harp
and everybody's so happy. And my mother
came from America, my stepmother, and
she was so happy and we had a big
celebration and I was start I started my
new job which is relaxing
and uh then somebody came the wants to
see you. This is the boss of the
monastery. He wants to see you now. Then
you have to run you know then go to the
Abid. Then I said yes sir. And he never
said any good thing about me for 25
years. Then he said, "Okay, pretty good.
600 years you are the first foreign
person to finish ging in our monastery."
Then
not so bad.
Then he said, "But you're, you know,
white guy." He said, "No, you have to go
to New York and you start business."
Then I said I hate business. I hate
business people. Then then you have to
do what business? Diamond business.
I hate diamond business. Okay. You have
to do it. Then you make uh like a
million dollars in one year
because we want to examination. Do you
understand karma? Can you use karma to
make a million dollars in one year? then
this is your second examination
and I I didn't go I didn't want to go so
I said okay I I delay delay delay then
finally he said you have to go tomorrow
all right I will go and we went to New
York then uh he said the money we will
give to the poor people you don't keep
the money you know so we worked with a
company we use karma we only use karma
in the company. We started with three
people. Now that company is $250 million
uh per year and we have 10,000 people.
Then he said, "Okay, you pass
examination here. Uh I only get my money
I give to the refugees, poor people." So
then people ask me, uh will you write a
book about how to do that? We also want
to do it, you know. uh how to use karma
to make business. So I wrote a book it's
called diamond color. There are some
some there a few
uh
then many countries asked me to come to
their country and talk about
how to use karma to make a business you
know even though I don't like business
then uh I was in China and uh very I
like to go there I have many good
friends there now very close we are very
close now and I was in Guangjo I This is
South China and we are giving a business
talk
about how to use
karma in the business. Then one lady
said, "Excuse me, excuse me." You know,
I said, "What? What?" She said, "I have
question." What do you call when he I
have question? You know, I said, "What
is the question?" She said, "So, you can
use karma to make money?" I said, "Yeah,
that's what I'm teaching you." Then she
said, "Can you use karma to fix your
husband?"
And I said, "They don't teach us in the
monastery." But uh yeah, you can do you
can do you can use karma to fix your
husband. Then she then one guy raised
his hand.
What's the question? Can you use karma
to fix wife also?
Then I said, "Yeah, you can do it." Then
business talk collapsed.
No more business talk. Everybody has a
question about wife, question about
husband. One lady said, "I don't have a
boyfriend. I want a boyfriend. Can I use
karma? Can I make a boyfriend with
karma?"
Yes. Yes, you can do it. You know, then
then people ask me, I have a book here.
For I don't know, for 10 years, people
ask me thousands of questions about
their husband or their girlfriend. Then
I took the 100 best questions which
everyone asked me in the in the whole
world. Many many people asked me
questions. Some people asked me question
here two years ago. I put it in the
book. Okay. It's you have to check
inside. Uh so I made a book uh 100
questions about your relationship. You
can't buy it. Okay. It's not out here.
It's on Amazon. But uh it's now number
one in Germany for
uh never mind
relationship book but it didn't come out
anyway. Uh so I thought tonight we can
talk about uh and you can look at it if
you want but how to use karma in your
relationships. you know how to change
your husband or change your wife or if
you want to find a partner, how to find
a partner. Then uh my own story about
partner uh my father and mother they
used to fight with each other. They uh
drink alcohol
and they used to fight and uh finally
they split when I was uh 12 years old. I
think mother went to Arizona, father
went to California. Then uh very sad for
us. We are four brothers and parents
split up and then we have to one month
go stay with father and one month stay
with mother you know like that then we
will ask the father when will you come
back home you know and then he said I I
won't come home then we said why don't
you love the mother he said I love her I
love her so much and he said so come
home and he said I can't stay with her
you know then Uh we asked the mother
don't you love father? Yes I love him I
cannot stay with him. Then I thought
this is my uh first information about
relationships you know then we are
confused you know what's wrong you know
why people do like that you know we
didn't understand then I had my first uh
girlfriend you can see here I hope she
doesn't have Facebook
uh
page one. Okay. Her name is Paula
Monday. Okay. I'm sorry Paula M. I have
to talk about our relationship. I was in
sixth class, sixth grade. Then uh I came
to the school and in our school the
students shouldn't talk to each other.
So we are running note and we are
passing notes like that. you know and uh
if you like a girl you shouldn't give
the note to her you have to give to her
friend and then her friend will give the
note to her you see so I got a note from
my friend and it said
her friend she gave it to her friend her
friend gave to my friend my friend gave
to me some paper you know then I like he
said I like you
Monday saying Mike I like you and I'm
like
you know then uh after a while her she
told her friend to tell my friend to
tell me she wants to be my girlfriend
you know I'm okay we can do then in my
school when you are 12 years old you
have to have a ring special ring
to give to the girl you know so
she said you're supposed to give me a
ring then I in my life I never stole any
money. But I stole one thing in my
mother's purse. I stole $5. $5, right?
Like that. And uh I bought a ring for
Paul one day. Right. Then I said, "Meet
me in the football field. Then we went
to the football field. Then there are
many what do you call seats like that
bleacher?
Many rows seat. She sat on the bottom. I
sat on the top. Then I said, "You want
to go? you want to be my girlfriend? She
said, "Yes." Then I said, "Do you want
to wear my ring?" She said, "Yes." Then
I said, "Okay, I got a ring for you."
Then I threw it to her. Then she cut it.
She put on then we are girlfriend and
boyfriend. And then uh but we didn't do
anything. Okay. Just you wear the wings.
We are too scared to do anything.
Then after I think two or 3 months uh
she gave to her friend a paper her
friend gave to my friend and he gave to
me and you know it's closed up like this
and I open it in the class you have to
do secretly right
then the ring fell out then goes
everybody in the class is like
then the teacher also like what is the
what is
Then it's her ring that I ring. I don't
want to be your girlfriend now. And I
say, I don't know why she wants to be my
girlfriend. Now I don't know why she
doesn't want to be my girlfriend.
Then that was my beginning of my uh
girlfriends first one. Then it didn't
change after that. It was the same. You
know, every class, seventh class, 8th
class, ninth class, it's the same, you
know. And it seems like relationship
starts like this. You know, you see
somebody, you know, in the coffee shop
and you sit next to them and you say I,
you know, I see you are reading a
newspaper. I also read a newspaper
and uh and then you start to talk and
and then you say you want to go out with
them and they're like, "Yeah, yeah." And
then you're so excited, you're so happy,
you know, and you think, "Oh, this one
will be better than Paula one day, you
know, and uh you you go out with them."
I remember the girl, I took her to
Chinese restaurant and we had Chinese
food and she really enjoy and then you
start to first kiss and then other
things and you feel very happy, you
know. Um it's like that. Then one day
you say, "Let's go to the restaurant."
One restaurant. Let's go to the Chinese
restaurant. The first Chinese restaurant
where we we we went out together. I
don't like Chinese food.
But you went many times. I just want to
make you happy. Actually, I don't like
Chinese food. Then you But I like
Chinese food. Can we go? But you want me
to go to Chinese food? I don't like
Chinese food. You like Chinese food.
Then that's the first argument. First
point, right? Then second fight, third
fight, fourth fight, then after 6 months
you are fighting all the time, you are
always fighting, you know. And then then
you say okay. Then you leave, you know,
you go. Then uh
someone say to you, who do you hate in
the world the most? You say my old
girlfriend, my ex-wife, my ex-boyfriend.
You know, they start who do you I hate
them.
Will you come to the party with me? Is
he going to be there? I won't go. He
knows like you know that right? It
happens like that. Every relationship it
starts very nice and very exciting and
then first kiss and other things and
then then it goes down. It seems like
that you know then I thought I should
become a monk you know this is hopeless.
It's not possible to have a
relationship. It never works. always
some problem after then uh my teacher
you know in my monastery we talk about
relationship and I said oh I told my
llama my llama is old Tibetan llama we
stay together for 25 years he's tough
tough old llama you know then I said
not true okay here we go
you have to ask I'm going to ask
question you have to give me answer okay
what is this
It depends. Okay. Second question. If a
dog comes in here, a small puppy dog,
and I go, you know, I go like this, what
will they do with this thing?
Put a chew on it. Okay. Does the dog see
this thing as a pen or not?
No. They see something. Oh, look.
Something to chew. Okay.
Dog sees chewy.
Human sees a pet. Next question.
Who's correct? Dog or human. Who's
correct? Both. Both. You can say both. I
think you can say both. Only one guy in
America in Florida.
He said no. No. Dog is both.
[Music]
Only one guy in the whole world.
Dog is wrong.
Dog catch you. It's okay. The dog said
to the person, why are you running? It
tastes so good.
So, uh, of course, both are correct.
Okay, now difficult question. Okay, you
have to learn this question. Why?
Tonight we are talking about partner,
your boyfriend or girlfriend or wife or
husband. We want to make a perfect one.
Perfect.
If you already have a partner, you can
fix that. You can upgrade to business
class.
Okay. Then if you don't have partner,
you can you can make one with karma.
Okay. I'm teaching you karma. This is
new thing, new system. Okay. Does it
work? Yes. Why? $200 million. Okay. It
works. It works. Okay. No, it works. I
don't know anything about business.
Nothing. But I know about the pen. Okay.
So learn learn the pen. Okay. Next
question. Difficult question. If I put
this thing here,
all the people go out and all the dogs
go out
at that time. Which one is it? Pen or
two?
All the people are gone. All the dogs
are gone. This thing is here. Now what
is it? Which one? Neither. Yeah. Who's
that? Neither. Yeah. Good. In in most
countries, somebody in the front will
go.
It's neither one. And you're correct.
You're right. It's neither one. At that
time, no dog, no person. Then it's just
some yellow thing, right? Some yellow
thing. If the dog comes in, it becomes a
cute guy. Cute. If the person comes in,
it becomes a Okay. If both of them come
in
becomes both. Okay. And if they both
leave
then it's
nothing. Just nothing. That's the
meaning of emptiness. Okay. That's the
meaning of emptiness. Uh what you call
that's the meaning of emptiness. How can
you use that to find a good boyfriend or
girlfriend? How can you use that to fix
your wife or your husband? Okay, this
tonight we have to learn that. Okay, you
don't have to struggle. You don't have
to fight. Some lady came to me. Okay, I
give you a real Oh, no. I have to ask
you one more question.
So is when I see pen
is the pen coming from me from my mind
or is the pen coming from the pen? Which
one? You. You must be from me. Must be
from me. Why?
Your perception.
The dog doesn't see pen. If the pen is
coming from the pen, the dog will see a
pen. The dog will write some poetry
to his dog girlfriend.
You have a nice tail.
But they don't do that. Why? The the pen
is not coming from the pen. The pen is
coming from me. It must be true because
the dog doesn't see a pen. It must be
true. Okay. So, can I close my eyes and
I say I don't want a pen. I want a big
diamond. You know it's coming from me.
You know I will use positive thinking.
I want a diamond. I want a diamond. It's
coming from me.
Oh, it's still okay. Okay. It's very
interesting. Is it coming from me? Yes.
Can I control it?
No. Okay. Then why is it coming from me?
There's a seed in my mind. I have a
scene in my mind. Okay, it's very
interesting. Then that scene when I look
at this thing when when Michael looks at
this thing, that scene opens in one
second. I I go like this.
What is this? And when I go like this,
if you are human, a seed opens in your
mind and you see a pen. The pen is
coming from the seed in your mind to
this thing. It's this big.
The the pen in your mind is this big.
Karma opens. Karma means a seed, right?
Karma means a seed. The seed opens in
your mind. A little picture comes out
and oh look pen. You see it's very fast.
You can do 65 times in 1 second. Buddha
said 65 times in 1 second.
Divide 1 second by 65. That's how long
it takes for the seal to open and come
to this pet. Okay? And you are doing it
with everything. Okay? This building,
Oslo, your fans, your hand, me,
everything's coming from you.
Everything's coming out of your way. So
if you don't like my talk, it's your
fault.
Okay?
Now everything is coming from from our
mind. Okay. From a seed in my mind.
Question question how to plant the seed.
How to plant the seed. Then you can make
$200 million. It's easy. Just plant the
seed. Don't go work so hard. I work 6
months. I take six month vacation. And
this is correct system. Right? Some
people work 50 weeks. They take two week
vacation. I say you are crazy. You are
crazy. Okay. Work 6 months, relax 6
months.
Good system. Okay. If you understand the
seed, you can do that. Okay. You just
have to understand the seeding diamond
sutra. Just understand tonight. You can
understand then use it for the rest of
your life. John and Leon can teach you.
They studied it for many years. You are
very lucky to have them. I think you
should kidnap them and tie them up. If I
am from Norway, I will tie them up. You
cannot go home. Okay?
Cuz they are really good teachers. They
can teach you the details, but tonight I
will just teach you roughly. So
question, how do I if I want to have a
boyfriend or girlfriend? Let's say I
don't have a partner. I try to have a
partner but poly Monday.
Then how do I how do I put the seed for
a good partner? How do I plant the seed?
Then they will come to you. You don't
have to work to find them. I will give
you a story. Okay? Then we will play one
song with okay. I'll give you a short
story. There's a woman in uh New York.
She's uh studying with me. She's a yoga
teacher. Good yoga teacher. The yoga
teacher who understands this thing is a
great yoga teacher. Okay, they are
teaching you both. They are teaching you
uh utanasana and pimutanasana and
pashimotasa but they are also teaching
you the meaning. Right? So she came to
me she said uh she's also architect
and she said
will you do mo will you do more? Mo
means in Tibet uh what do you call dice?
What do you call in Norwegian?
Just to play a game.
[Music]
Okay.
Then uh there's then the monk in Tibet,
we have to uh people will ask us a
question. Should I rent this apartment
or not? Then will you do more for me?
Please do more. Then we have to you know
and we say oh no you shouldn't rent that
apartment. Okay. So people come to me
with question.
Uh she come to me will you do more? Okay
I will do more. Uh
what's your question? I have a question
about my boyfriend.
What's a question? I don't have a
boyfriend. And I said so why are you
asking me question? I want to know
should I look for him in the nightclub
or should I look for him in the
internet?
Please do more.
And I said okay then we supposed to be
very serious you know
[Music]
we don't use hand we use kapali kapali
means this uh what do you call skull
from a person we use skull like that
supposed to be very serious you know
then uh you should put your eyes like
that
then you should say some mantra
internet or nightclub.
Then you have to throw. You can't go
like this. Okay. You have to go and
she said, "Is he in the nightclub?"
No.
Oh, that's good. Why?
The boy who goes to the nightclub is the
boy who goes to the nightclub.
You can't trust him. He will go to the
nightclub cuz I'm black. So he's in the
internet.
No, not in the internet. Oh, that's
good. Why? The boy who lives in
internet, he likes a laptop more than
his girlfriend.
He likes Facebook more than his
girlfriend. So where will I find him?
Where should I find him?
You go to we call nursing home. Old
person's
home. What do you call in Norwegian
where the old people stay?
Like that you go there. This is like
but
I want a young boyfriend.
I said no no you don't understand. Uh
you have to plant the seed. If you want
a partner you must plant a partner seed
in your own life. Then I said why do you
want boyfriend? I'm I feel lonely. I'm
happy. I have a good job. I teach yoga.
I'm happy uh all day I'm happy but when
I go by myself nobody to talk to you
know I want someone I can talk to them
he will hug me you know I want a
boyfriend I I feel lonely so I said in
this system diamond cut jing system what
you want you must give to another person
same thing you see if you want money you
have to
money money to other people. You have to
to plant the karma. You have to give to
another person. Like if I want to make
million dollars, I should help the other
person to make money. I must I must
plant the seed. It's the only way. If I
want to be healthy, should I do yoga?
Yes or no?
Some people hurt their neck in yoga
because they come from a yoga class.
What's wrong? I told the yoga class you
know and uh yoga cannot help you. If you
help sick people
then go to yoga. You yoga make you
strong. If you don't help sick people
and you go to yoga
you will hurt yourself. Okay. It's true.
The the the muscle is coming from
helping sick people and then the yoga
will help you. It's very interesting.
Right. You didn't hear that in the other
yoga studios, I think, but it's true.
Okay. So, if you want to find a
boyfriend or you want a good partner,
you have to go find an old person and
help them who has no family. Okay.
Today, before we came here, where did we
go?
We all went to the what's the place
called? Mango. Mango. Pale. Pale. Pale.
What was the other store called? Mango.
No, the with a sweater in Dale of
Norway. Oh, that one. Dale of Norway.
And I bought uh some nice sweater
for who? Just before we ran there and we
ran back. Then I didn't talk. Then we
bought some clothes for my old lady. I
have old lady. She's 87 years old, you
know. And I I help her. I take care of
her. Why
I want to plant karma? She is my karma
planting garden, the old woman. Then I
always when I come back Monday we go
home uh to my place.
Then I go to her house. I'm like this,
you know, and she's always, "What's
behind your back?" You know, I have
something for you. From where? from
Norway. Beautiful sweater. Look, you
know, and then she's very happy. I am
planting seed with her. She is my garden
and I plant for 20 years. I am planting
my seed with her. Okay? You must if you
want to have a good partner.
You need a old person and you have to
visit them once a week. Okay? Must. No
choice. In this system, you have to no
choice. It's very interesting. Okay,
this is how you plant karma. And then
the boy will come to you or the woman
will come to you. You don't have to go
look on the internet. You don't have to
go to nightclub. You can sit in the
coffee shop. They will come in the door.
They will sit next to you. Okay. Uh the
perfect partner. Okay. Just plant them
here. Why?
Okay. Boyfriend also coming from you.
Where from here? How plant the seed? How
to plant the seed? Help old person who
has no family. Help them. Plant the
seed. Then the boyfriend will come. It's
very beautiful system. Easy. It's no
easy. You don't have to look on the
internet for 10 hours, you know. Oh,
this one looks good. Oh no, he's a
problem. You know, or the love is
terrible. You have to breathe all the
cigarette smoke. And okay, this system
is very easy. Visit the old person. Make
them happy. Plant the seed
and the boyfriend will come. This is
karma. This is a new system. This is a
new system. If you want $200 million,
plant the seed. If you want a beautiful
partner, who gets more beautiful every
year, then help the old people. Help the
old people. Okay? This is a new system.
Do they have to be old? Doesn't have to
be old. Can be a child also.
can be lonely person in your job.
Someone who is lonely only has to be
lonely. Okay. Uh old people are easy to
find.
No. And there are many many old people.
Okay. But I'm telling you the truth. You
don't have to work a whole year like
that. I only work six months. But I know
how to plant the seed. Then the money
comes. Okay? You just plant karma. You
want to be super yoga teacher. Then help
the sick people. Then then the yoga will
change. Your yoga will change because
your yoga is coming from you. Okay? Yoga
is coming from your mind. Okay? Then it
will make you strong. Plant the seed
then do yoga. It will be good. We're
going to play one song. Is that okay?
Good.
We'll play one song. Okay.
People all the time. They help people
all all the time. Old people. But for 5
years, he didn't have a boyfriend.
So, what happened to the karma? Where's
the karma? Uh,
you plant a karma. How do you plan a
karma?
When you go to visit the old person or
the young person with only when you go
there you plant karma. How?
Karma is planted in your own mind. I
cannot plant your karma. You have to
plant your own karma. If you want to
make $200 million or you want to be a
yoga teacher or or you want to have a
nice partner, you have to plan. I cannot
do for you. If I could do, I will do
from America. I don't have to fly here.
You see,
you have to plant your own karma. How?
You must visit lonely person yourself.
How does the karma come into your mind?
How does the seed come into your mind?
You are watching yourself with your own
eyes. Okay. You are go to the old
person's house. You are talking to them.
Tell me about your when you were young.
Tell me some story from your life. They
will tell you the same story every week
because they forgot. They told you
before. Okay. I'm similar. Then uh
when you help them, when you visit them,
when you're helping them and nice to
them, who is watching?
They are watching and you are watching.
Your mind, your eyes are like a camera.
Like there's this video camera, right?
So when you talking to the old person,
you are hearing yourself. This plants a
seed. Okay? When you do something good,
you are watching yourself and that puts
a seed in your mind. Okay? That's how
you get a seed.
Then then you can say I have many
friends they helped their grandmother
they helped their grandfather they
didn't get a boyfriend then what
happened to the karma the karma is there
nothing can stop karma nothing if you
help somebody good thing will happen to
you 10 times more 20 times more 30 times
more 200 million times more it will come
back okay otherwise you give $10 and $10
come back it's a waste of
Okay, the seed is small, right? This
tree, this tree started from a a seed
that you can hold in your hand. Now that
tree can can break the house. If it
falls down, it will break that building.
You know, it came from this seed this
big. The seed in the mind is the same.
Okay. Plant a small seed for a nice
partner.
beautiful partner will come much much
you give the old person one hour a week
and then a man or a woman will come into
your life for your whole life and more
beautiful every year why you planted the
seed how big was the seed one hour
how big is the the boyfriend or the
girlfriend who comes out of the seed
whole life okay it's it's the nature of
seed small seed
big tree. Okay, you just have to plant
it, then relax. Okay, everyone's so
uptight. I have to have a boyfriend. I
couldn't find an internet. Relax. Just
plant a seed. Plant a seed, then relax.
Okay, then he has to come. He doesn't
have choice. Okay, he will come. I'm not
kidding. I planted many seeds for money.
I quit the business in 1999. I stopped
working. I don't do the business
anymore. Then I took yoga class. uh
Dharma Mitra in New York. I went to big
yoga teacher. He kills you for 2 hours
but afterward you can tell your friends
I went to Dharma Mitra and uh he kills
you. Then one guy came up to me in the
class he said you are man. I said yeah.
He said I want to shake your head. I
said okay thanks. He said okay bye. Then
I said wait what's your name? John. Then
I never met him in my life. I never met
him. Then that day I got email in the
evening.
Why didn't you thank me?
John from John. Why didn't you thank me?
Then I wrote him email. Why? Why should
I thank you? You Michael, you have I
have a rucksack bag I carry with me. He
said you look inside. Then I look
inside. There's an envelope. Look in the
envelope. there's a check $100,000
US. Then I'm like,
then I sent him email, you know.
Thank you.
I said, why you give me money? I don't
know you. I never met you in my life.
Why you give me money? He says, I also
don't know why. I just want to give you
you know it means I planted the seed
before then even I don't want money the
money will chase me okay I'm running the
money is running faster when it comes
really I'm not kidding who who will give
you $100,000 in yoga class it's it's
strange you know if you plant a seed for
a good partner they will come they don't
have a choice they must come okay it's
very Beautiful. But you have to take
good care of the seed. All right? You
must know how to plant the seed. If I
have a what do you call watermelon seed
and I throw it here, will it grow? It
won't grow. Is it a good seed? Yeah, it
is a good seed. You put in the wrong
place. You don't know how to take care
of the seed. Don't put water. Don't put
soil. No sunlight. How can it grow? It
won't grow. Okay. All of the karma in
you have uh 20 million 200 million karma
in your mind already. You already have
everybody here has you have the seeds.
You helped many people and you helped
many old people. Everybody you did some
good things in your life. The seeds are
there but there's no water. Okay, I will
teach you the water. Okay,
there's a special meditation they can
teach you. John can teach you, Leon can
teach you. It's called we call coffee
meditation. Okay, coffee meditation. You
can do like this, right?
Then you can
that's not coffee. Okay, don't do that.
My teacher taught me, he said, "Go like
this.
This is meditation."
Then I said to my teacher, "That's not
meditation." He said, "It is
meditation." Then I said, "Where do you
do it?" He said, "On your bed."
Then when before you go to sleep, then
what am I supposed to think about?
Think about the old woman which you
helped today.
You took her to the coffee shop, right?
I take my old lady to I'm going to give
her the Norwegian sweater in the coffee
shop. Okay, I will take her to coffee.
She dresses up. She puts on her makeup.
We go out. Then I say, "Come to the
coffee shop. I have sweater for you."
You know and then when you come home
you have a scene in your mind who put it
there.
You did how?
You were there when you came with the
sweater. Okay, that's all your mind is
that video camera. It makes the seed in
your mind. Then go home, eat your
dinner, clean up, take your bath, then
lay down on your bed and say, "Oh, today
I did a good thing." What? I took the
old lady to the coffee shop. I gave her,
what's it called? Dale of Norway. Yeah.
Dale of Norway. Dale of Norway. Dale of
Norway. I gave her Dale of Norway
sweater. I will not tell her it was 50%
discount.
Then uh it has a price big price tag.
Then uh she was so happy and she put on
a sweater and she's looking in the
mirror and when I think about her and I
think about how happy she was. This is
the water on the karma. This is the for
the seed, the karma seed. There's a
water on the seed and it will grow
faster. It will grow very fast and then
you will have a beautiful relationship.
Okay, that's all. Okay, people don't
know how to put water on the karma. Now
you know where
on the bed when
before you go to sleep.
What kind of meditation? Think about the
people you helped today. Think about
what good thing you did today. This is
water on the karma. then $200 million
will come. Okay, I'm not kidding. You
can check. We own jewelry.com. The name
cost $21 million. The name jewelry.com
cost $21 million. Okay, how? Just relax.
Think about the good thing which you did
for other people and that makes the
scene go fast. Okay. Is it difficult?
It's easier than yoga, right?
Okay. All right, then I'm telling you
big secret. This is $200 million secret
or boyfriend secret. Okay, you can plant
that. You don't have to work so hard.
Help somebody else to get the secret you
want. Then come home, do this
meditation. We call in Tibetan we call
shea.
Say she
didn't just do that. Didn't the
boyfriend you you can't run away from
the boyfriend. He will chase you. All
right. I'm not kidding. Okay. Uh I
thought we take a break, but I have a
question for you.
We will take a break. It's okay, John.
Yeah. Uh but I have a question for you.
Uh someone asked me in China, when I was
in China, they asked a very good
question. One guy raised his hand and he
said, "I I understand your system. It
sounds good to me. It's logical. If I
help someone to who is lonely,
it plants karma for boyfriend. If I help
poor people, money will come to me. I
like your system. It sounds good to me.
But in China, when we are young, our
mother, our father, they will tell us,
"Help other people. Do good for other
people. But don't ask them for
something. Give me something. This is
not love. I This is not love. This is
business.
Oh, I will take you to the coffee shop.
I will give you a sweater from Dale of
Norway. If you if I get a boyfriend, if
I get a girlfriend. It's like a
business, right? Or I will help the poor
people. Why? I want more money. You see,
this is not love. This is like strange,
selfish. I want something from you so I
will be nice to you. You know then I
Chinese person asked me this this sounds
strange to Chinese people our mother our
father told us when you give something
to somebody or you help the old person
do it from love don't ask them for
something you know don't say give me now
give me something it should be from love
okay so what is my answer for that
after refreshments okay there's
something very interesting thing. Okay,
there's something very interesting. If
you understand how to plant seed, if you
understand this new system, when you use
it, you help the whole world. You are
helping the whole world. You are making
peace in the world. You are helping
everybody in the world. If you take the
old woman to the coffee shop and give
her a sweater from Dale of Norway,
you are helping the whole world. You are
making peace in the world. Why? How? I'm
not going to tell you.
After refreshments is a blackmailing
you have to come back. Okay. Then no. In
the second half, we have to talk about
this uh question, right?
How to make peace in the world by using
this system. We talk about that. Okay.
So, we take a break.
Look at page.
Page three.
And it's called ordering your new car.
But it means your new boyfriend or
girlfriend.
Then uh when you go to buy a car, right,
you have to ask uh I want this color or
I want this kind of stereo or you have
to tell them what kind of car. It's not
enough just to say I want a car. Excuse
me. You have to tell them what kind of
car, what color, what shape. Same with
the partner. Okay? You have to decide
what do you want in your partner. Some
people say I want my partner to help me
a lot, you know, or I want a partner who
has a job
[Music]
or uh I want a partner who doesn't get
tired of sex. After 3 weeks like that,
you know, people want uh different
things in the apartment in uh
we meet a new person, right? And we say,
"Okay, this one looks pretty good. It's
about 75% good.
25%
not so good." You see what I mean? And
then you have to make a decision. If
they say you want to be my boyfriend or
you want to be my husband then you have
to say I don't know you're only 75%.
You know you are not 100%. Then we we
have to make a decision right I like
this person uh I like to stay with them
maybe I would like to get married to
this person but some things I don't like
about them. I I want to fix some things
about them. So then you have to you can
do two things. You see for example many
women told me in the beginning of my
marriage my husband used to come home
and he always gives me hug. When he
comes home from work he he says honey
and he gives me a hug you know. Now he
comes home from work. He opens the door.
He goes like this to his laptop
and then does Facebook, you know, and he
doesn't he only hugs his computer. He
doesn't hug me, you see. Then do you
want to leave your husband? No. I love
him. I like him. So what will you do to
fix him about affection? I want more
love from him.
Some people tell me uh I will talk to
him. I will talk to him for 3 4 hours.
When you come home, you should give me a
hug. You know, it's good to give me a
hug. I want a hug. Every husband should
come home and give the wife a hug. Then
of course, next day, what will he do? He
will come home. Okay, here come give you
a hug.
Then it doesn't feel happy, you know.
He's just like that. Is that enough?
It's not fun. If you have to negotiate
for a hug, the hug is not so good. The
hug should be coming from
their heart, right? Or some people say,
"Okay, if you don't give me a hug, I
won't cook dinner."
Like blackmail
the husband. You see this system? This
is the old system. Why?
Sometimes you you fight for a hug. You
fight for affection and they don't give
you. Sometimes they do give you. Okay?
Sometimes you say, "Okay, no dinner."
They will give you affection. Sometimes
they will get angry. Okay? It doesn't
work.
That's not the way to get affection from
your partner, right? To fix them. How
should you fix your partner?
Four steps we did before, right? She
number one. What?
Number one is what do you want? Decide
what do you want? Okay. What do you
want? I want my husband to give me some
affection, some love. Before when we
started, he used to give me, but now he
doesn't, you know. So, I want to change
it. Okay. Number one, I want husband to
give me a hug. Then number two, what
should we do?
Help an old lady. Yeah. Or help an old
lady. Or find someone who not getting
affection. Okay. Be friendly to people.
Okay. Smile to them. Okay. Just on the
street or in the store or at the yoga
class, you know, be friendly. Can I help
you? Look, uh, I'll help you with your
map or you know, you are doing
headstand. Let me help you. Okay. Like
that. be friendly to another person.
Okay? It puts a ceiling on my then you
come home then husband wants to give you
hug you see but you have to put water on
the seat. What is the water
reflection?
Where? On your bed. On your bed. When
before you go to sleep, it's very good
before you go to sleep. Why?
The mind you will remember all night.
Whole night that seed will grow all
night. You see? So before you go to
sleep,
think about the good things you did
today. Okay? Oh, today I was friendly to
everybody at yoga studio. I went to the
yoga I helped everybody.
I did a good thing. This is water on the
sea. Okay? Then send it to your husband.
Okay? Send that power to your husband.
Then after 2 weeks, he will start to hug
you. Okay? Understand? No discussion, no
fighting,
no not cooking.
Okay? Just plant the seed where
on the street in the grocery store be at
the yoga class. Be friendly to other
people. Show them some
smile.
Then think about it when you go home. I
did a good thing. Now I send it to
change my husband. Then he will give you
hug. You don't have to fight with him
and you don't have to argue with him.
just plant the seed. Okay, it's better.
Everything you want, you can have. Okay,
now we're going to go to page uh page
four.
That tree outside,
did it come from a seed? Yes or no?
Yes, it came from a seed. How big was
the seed?
It's this big, right? It's this big. The
seed for the string is that big.
Where is the seed now?
Which br
is the seed
now.
It's gone. The seed is gone. The tree
came up and the seed finishes. Okay.
The tree killed the seed.
The seed gave life to the tree. Then the
tree kills the seed. All things are
coming from seeds. The pen is coming
from a seed, right? In your mind. Okay.
The husband is coming from the seed.
And the tree is coming from a seed.
Will the tree die or not?
Will this tree die?
Yeah. Of course it will die. Why?
Because the seed's power finished. The
power of the seed finished. Then the
seed the tree will die. The tree must
die. Why?
Every day the tree is alive. It is using
seeds power up like a debit card. You
have debit cards? Yeah. Yeah.
I had big credit card negotiation at
Dale and Lori. Uh you have credit debit
card. You come into this life with a
debit card. You come into this life with
a body. It is made by seeds. Every day
that you live, that debit card is going
down. One day cost you more seeds. Okay?
And then one day debit card will finish.
Someone asked me a question during the
break. You know, does everybody have to
die? Is everything impermanent? Buddha
said everything is impermanent.
Everything has to die. It's not true.
Okay. He he said if you don't understand
seeds, everything will die. If you
understand seeds,
you just plant more seeds. Okay. For
example,
uh you want money. Okay. Let's say you
I'm not a big uh what do you call? I
don't want to be rich. I want to have
enough money. I can go
to Los Angeles. If I want to go to Los
Angeles, I can relax. I can go. I don't
have to worry. I don't have enough
money. You see, I don't want to have
three uh Mercedes-Benz
because I only have one body.
Okay?
More thing is more trouble. More things
are more trouble. But I would like to
have enough money to to do what I like
to do. And I don't have to think about
money. I just have enough like that. I
would like that. You know, that's good.
I don't want to be rich. How do I get
money in this system? Four steps.
First one.
Number one, decide what do you want. I
want enough money to be independent. I
can do anything I want. Number one.
Number two.
Find someone else who needs money. Find
someone who needs money. Who wants
money? Okay. Number three.
Give them help them to make money.
Number four
on your bed. Say, "Oh, today I have
someone to make the money. I did a good
thing." That's the water. If you don't
do the water, this system doesn't work.
Okay? In this system, you must be happy
about who?
Me. Okay? Yourself. Okay? In this
system, you must be happy about
yourself. Number four, always the same.
Today I did a good thing. What? I helped
someone to make some money. You know, I
did a good thing. Then that seed will
come back. That seed will grow.
Some money will come to you. Then what
will happen?
The seed will finish and the tree will
die. What?
The money will Yeah. When the money
comes, we invest. You see, you don't
have to give all of it. Just give half
of it or 5% 10% when nobody wants you
plant more seeds. Okay.
The woman who asked me to do the mole,
she went to nursing home, she helped the
old lady. Uh after a few months into her
yoga class came a very beautiful man.
Then she called me Gian what this system
works. I said I know
she said are you busy next month? Why
will you come to New York? Why? We are
getting married. We need a monk to do
the She's Chinese. She said I need a
monk. Okay, I will come. Then I went to
New York uh to do the wedding, right?
And it was fun for me because I helped
to plant the boy.
I said, "We did a good job. Look, he's
handsome. He has a good job. He's a nice
guy. We planted a good one. You know, we
are heads." Then we are eating the
wedding cake together and we are having
fun. You know, everybody's relaxed. Then
I said, "Come sit down with me with the
boy." I said, "Come, let's talk." Then I
said, uh, I'm so happy you got married.
Yes, thank you so much. Your mo is very
good. Then I said, uh,
so how is the old lady?
Then she's like,
I was very busy. I have to buy the
wedding dress. Then I have to make the
wedding food. Then I had to make the
invitation. I didn't have time to visit
her, you know. Then I said, "Sit down.
We have a problem."
What happens if you stop planting seeds?
You will have your first fight.
Actually, I don't like Chinese food.
Remember,
you see, he will say or she will say, "I
don't like Chinese food. I don't want to
go there with you today. I want to do a
different movie. I don't like that film.
I like this other thing. Fighting will
start. Problem will start. Why? The city
is dying. The seed is dying. Then I told
them you have no choice. You have to go
to the world. You cannot stop. Okay? You
if you stop planting seeds, the tree
will die. Okay? The all relationship
will go like this. Companies go like
this.
Human body goes like this. Okay?
Government goes like this. Countries go
like this. Okay. All of them strong
strong storm then get old die. This is
the tree also. And this building will
fall down one day. Okay. It's always the
same. You don't have a choice. I got mad
at her. You have to go to the old lady
with him.
Okay. Got it? If you're having trouble
in your relationship, go together to
help a lonely person. Okay, I'm giving
you a secret how to plant new seeds.
Okay, if you plant new seeds, that
relationship will get better every year,
more and more happy, more and more
beautiful. Okay, if you don't do that,
then what will happen? Chinese
restaurant.
Okay, actually I don't like Chinese
food. You see what I mean? Then we'll
start the fighting and the fighting will
get more and more and then one day you
will wake up. Okay. You don't have to.
It's you can have a relationship which
is permanent. You can have a
relationship which gets better every
year for 50 years, 60 years. You can
have
Is it possible to stop death?
Yeah, it's possible. Your body also
coming from you from seed. Okay. But you
have to plant more seeds like how take
care of sick people teach yoga
take teacher train you know become yoga
teacher help other people with their
life and your life will will get
stronger and longer someone came to me
in the break they said I have foot
problem can I fix it with the seeds
who's it coming from your foot.
It's coming. You know, I had a foot
problem also. I was what you call
crippled. I couldn't walk sometimes. Now
I do ballet. Last week in France, I was
doing ballet. Okay. I'm old. Okay. I
started ballet when I was 50. Uh because
I want to say you to the foot.
You are going to change. I'm going to
change because you are coming from me.
You are like a pen. And now I do ballet.
Okay. It's beautiful. You can change
your life. You can change everything.
Changing partner is easy. Food is more
difficult.
But you can do both. You can do
everything. Okay. Uh,
next page.
92 92.
Oh, we have a problem. Let me see.
Okay. So, I'm going to go to page six
and then we will finish and we'll press
some salt. Is that okay? One last one.
Okay. Uh
before the bread, I asked you a
question. What was the question?
Chinese person asked me a question. What
was it? Is this system selfish?
Is this system selfish?
We had some uh I had a talk with one man
in the break right about Krishna and
Arjuna, right? So in India there's a
famous uh story Bhagavat Bhagavad Gita
and uh somebody said uh Krishna said to
Arjun
when you do a good thing for another
person don't ask for something bad don't
be attached to the result of your karma
karma don't don't ask for something when
you give something it should be free
don't say oh give me something it should
be
Then in I said if you understand this
system
you can change the world you can help
the whole world it's not selfish
it's love when you use this system to
get a boyfriend
this will be love in Tibetan what they
call that
who said that
you're cheating
Bodhitta. Okay, you some of you heard
this word bodhisatta
or bhicha.
Then you know you say some prayer I hope
I can help all the living beings. You
know I hope I can help the whole world.
How can you help the whole world? You
know we can't even help ourselves. How
can you help seven billion people? You
know we don't have the power. You're not
Spider-Man.
You are not Iron Man. You're just a
person, you know. How can you help? How
can you make a prayer? I want to help
the whole world. If you understand this
system, if you use it, you are helping
the whole world automatically. Okay.
Why?
Okay. Let's say you go you don't have a
partner and you want a partner. Then
what do you have to do
in this system? Internet or or
nightclub? Which one?
Good. Good answer. Those are both
stupid.
Okay. What's the smart thing to do?
Yeah. Go visit an old person. Help a
lonely person. Okay. Plant the seed and
the boy will come. Okay. When the boy
comes. All right. You have a special
job. I'm going to tell you. All right.
Then we're finished. After
the boy is planted and when the boy
comes to you, okay, then you have to
call all of your friends on the
telephone and say, "Meet me at the
restaurant at 7:00." Okay? Call four or
five of your girlfriends. You meet me. I
have special news for you. You know,
come to the restaurant at 7:00.
Then call your new boy who you found.
Plant them. Plant them. Forget finding
them. Plant them. Finding means I have
to look. I have to look. I have to look
or money. I have to look for money. I
have to look. Forget that. Plant it and
relax. Okay? Just plant it and then it
has to come. It will come. Okay? So I
planted a boyfriend. Call the boyfriend
who you planted. Tell him to come to
your apartment. What time?
7:00. Same time.
I like it.
Tell him to come to your apartment at
7:00. When he comes, give him three
glasses of water. Big glasses of water.
Make him drink three glasses of water.
Then go to the restroom with him. Why?
You will be late.
7:30 you will reach the restaurant,
right? in the yard standing at the door.
All your friends are waiting for you.
Where is she? She has some surprise. Oh,
look. She's outside. Oh, she's coming
in. Huh? She has a boy. He's pretty
cute, you know. Uh, she didn't have
boyfriend for 5 years. Yeah, it's
probably her cousin. I think it's her
cousin.
Then come in with the boy. When you
reach the table, give him a big kiss.
No.
And then all the friends are like what
will they say?
Not a cousin.
Not not her cousin. Then must be
boyfriend. Yeah, it's a boyfriend.
How did she get the boyfriend? She's
silly.
Then of course you have to talk about
the food and politics and weather. Then
what will happen? He has to go to the
bathroom. He has to go to toilet.
because he gave me three glasses of
water.
Then he will say he's like this for 5
minutes.
Then finally he has to say excuse me I
have to go to the toilet. But when he
goes what will happen?
What will happen at the table?
Everybody say where where did you find
him? Where did you find him? Which
nightclub? Which internet? Nursing.
Nursing home.
He looks so young.
You have to say, "No, no, you don't
understand. I planted him in the nursing
home. It's a new system. It's a new
system.
No more.
No more nightclub. Nightclub is so
terrible. Smoke and loud music. You are
looking for someone you know it's so
difficult just plan it right he will
come right then what will happen
tomorrow next day what will happen
with your friends they will go to the
nursing home they will go to the nursing
home
some of them who are desperate
they will go to the nursing
Then what will happen? I'm serious. I'm
very serious.
What will happen?
They will get they will plan a
boyfriend. They will get a You know that
it's true. It's true. Then what will
happen? They will invite their friends.
Yeah. They tell their friends to go to
the restaurant. They get the three
glasses of water to
then what will happen?
Then those new people will go to the
nursing home after one year at the
nursing home. Long lines have
Can I meet her today? No.
Do you have any old woman?
Come back next week.
Tuesday 3:00. She has 10 minutes.
[Music]
I think old people who are lonely they
will become rare.
I think like a drug dealer there will be
old lady dealers
telephone number in old lady.
Okay. Okay.
I think maybe boys will meet girls in
the minds at the music hall. Right. And
uh I gave I taught this in Bulgaria last
year, two years ago. Last year. Yeah.
And uh there's one famous woman there.
And she used it. She planted a boy. And
she was walking. What do you call that
nice area in the middle? What's it
called? We went to the area. The park.
Yeah. So, she's walking in the place
like that and she's looking down and she
hits some guy and he she look up and he
look up and they're like
and she she called me. I got him. I
planted him. We bump into each other by
accident, you know. We are getting
married, you know, and she got married,
you know. It was very uh funny that she
said
years a revolution.
This is a boyfriend revolution.
Now everybody can have a boyfriend in
the world. You see? So what I'm saying
is when you go to visit the old lady
you must have this vision in your mind.
It will spread like computer virus. It
will spread. Everybody say where did you
get him? I didn't get him. I planted
him. How do you plan it? Go to the
nursing home. Then it will spread. One
person, two people, four people, eight
people, it will spread in the world.
Right? What will happen later? No more
lonely people anywhere. Okay? What with
money? If everybody understands
the only way to make money is to help
other people to make money, poor people
will become rare.
It will be difficult to find a poor
person. Right? It's true.
How to become young? How to become
healthy? Why?
Go to the hospital, then do yoga. Plant
a seed in the hospital, then do yoga.
Then the hospitals will be full of
people. Do you have any more sick people
to help? The nursing homes will be full
of people. Do you have any old women who
don't have a friend? And also the poor
people. Everybody's
Do you have any poor people? I met one
guy in America. He came to the store in
Detroit. Then after few days he came to
me, I have good news. What? I found her.
Foo one woman. She is sick. She is poor
and she is
Think the world will change. Okay. The
world will change. I gave this talk in
uh in China. I was in Guangjo
and uh I I asked I was a bunch of very
tough Chinese business guys, you know.
Then I asked them
after 3 days I asked them how do you
make money? They said plant it. I said,
"How do you plant money? Help other
people to make money."
Then I asked the question, these are
tough guys, you know. Then I said, "What
will happen if everybody does it?" And
they're all like,
then the guy said, "World peace. There
will be peace in the world because no
more hungry people, no more poor people,
no more lonely people, no more sick
people, everybody will have a friend.
This when you use this system, you are
creating world peace. Boyfriend
revolution.
Okay, you have to understand that it's
not uh selfish.
Uh it's not wrong to take the old woman
to the coffee shop. You are making world
peace. You are creating world peace.
Okay, last thing. Okay, then we go home
and we play one more song, right? You
ready? Uh our friend John and Leang,
we had a international uh conference,
big conference. Many countries came and
each country sent some video. So from
Oslo they you sent me a video or
somebody sent a video and it was Oslo
government or something. What was your
government? Commercial enterprise. Cell
phone. Yeah. Or cell phone. And they
said in uh Norway if the young person
takes the old person to the film the old
person gets free ticket or they both get
a free ticket. Then we said revolution
is beginning in Norway.
World revolution is beginning in Norway.
So when you help other people, you must
have a vision. That vision is called
bodhic.
That vision is called bodhic. What's the
vision?
I'm not going to the nursing home to
help one person. I am helping 7 billion
people. Okay? I am not helping one old
woman. I am helping 7 billion people
because I'm starting revolution.
Okay, you must think like that. Then the
karma has changed. Then the karma
changes and it will change the world.
Okay. And it will make you very